Preliminary Guide to the Office of Professional Development records, 1980-2002 RG0099
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Office of Professional Development records
1980-2006
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Office of Professional Development
RG0099
35.5 Linear Feet
Materials in this collection include programs sponsored by Office of Professional Development and other office records. The collections range in date from 1980-2002 and were transfered to University Archives in 1992.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
The majority of these records were transferred to University Archives in 1992.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Professional Development Office was formerly known as the Division of Continuing Education. As of December 17, 2004, the Office of the Registrar has assumed responsibility for maintaining all GW Solutions and Center for Professional Development academic records.
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include programs sponsored by Office of Professional Development and other office records. The collections range in date from 1980-2002 and were transfered to University Archives in 1992.
Formerly RG13.1.15
Collection Organization
Organized in three series: Sponsored programs, Personnel files, and Office files.
Washington (D.C.); Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); George Washington University; George Washington University. Division of Continuing Education
- Sponsored programs, 1981-1988; RG0099 Series 1; 2 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of mateirals related to programs sponsored by the Office of Professional Development, including general office records. They range in date from 1981-88, and were transferred to University Archives in 1992.
  Formerly ACC#172.
  This series has a container list in electronic form, please ask staff for assistance.
- Personnel files from the Professional Development Office, 1990-2000; RG0099 Series 2; 33 Linear feet (Box 6, Box 8, Box 4, Box 5, Box 1, Box 3, Box 2, Box 13, Box 15, Box 12, Box 14, Box 10, Box 11, Box 7, Box 9, Box 21B, Box 21A, Box 20, Box 19, Box 17B, Box 18, Box 17A, Box 16, Box 22)
  Includes CVs and Faculty Hire forms from employees in the Professional Development Office.
  The 22 boxes associated with this donation are not processed. Please see staff for assistance.
- Printed materials, 1980-2006; RG0099 Series 3; 0.5 Linear Feet 2 half size document boxes (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series includes brochures, schedule of classes, handouts, and student handbooks. They range in date from 1980-2002.
  Formerly vertical files
  - Center For Professional Development, 1980-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Continuing Education, Division of, 1982-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Continuing Education, Division of - Brochures, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Continuing Education, Division of - Center for Continuing Education in Washington Schedule of classes, 1982-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Continuing Education, Division of - Off-Campus Programs, 06/07/1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Continuing Education, Division of - Off-Campus Programs Schedules of classes, 1983-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Continuing Education, Division of Office of Conferences and Institutes, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Continuing Education, Division of -- President's Spouse seminars, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Center for Professional Development, 2001; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Event Management Certificate Program, 2000-2001; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Programs Schedule of Classes, 2006; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Graphics Standards Manual, 1996; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - GW Solutions, 2002; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Portfolio of Professional, Executive, and Customized Learning, 2003; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 6)